what's the best way to grow your email
list and is email marketing dead in 2024
truth is email marketing is as alive and
well today as it has ever been since
it's been in existence and people have
been saying for years oh email marketing
is dead there's all these new other ways
of marketing yet everything comes back
to email marketing and growing your
email list is the number one way to make
sure that you get clients in a coaching
online course mentoring or membership
business and so in this training I want
to walk you through the process of
creating a lead magnet to grow your
email list what is the right way to do
so so that you don't have to waste time
or wonder if you're doing it the right
way for those you that those of you that
I have not met yet my name is Jeremiah
Kowski and for the last 21 years I've
been helping coaches mentors and
trainers scale their businesses to tens
of millions of dollars online and I've
actually built multiple coaching and
mentoring businesses over $10 million
myself helped thousands of coaches and
mentors online get results scale to
multiple six and seven figures and I
focus specifically on helping people
make their first5 to
$25,000 per month in consistent
recurring Revenue in a coaching
membership or online course business
whether you're just starting out at zero
nobody knows who you are you don't have
a lot of tech skills I can get you to
where you want to be and and this is
something that I am probably one of the
best at I believe at helping people do
this whether it be the mindset part
whether it be the tech pieces how do you
Market how do you get clients online for
nearly any Niche not just Health not
just spirituality not just you know um
make money online offers but nearly
anything in this industry and it's what
I focused my entire career on and have a
passion for for the last 21 years and I
love getting people results it's one of
my number one things that I do so
obviously I don't do this because I I
don't want to get people results that's
my number one like that's the reason why
I even show up or get out of bed in the
morning is is that side of it so what I
want to do is I want to walk you through
the concept of why you need to create a
lead magnet first off I'm going to touch
on this just real briefly for those of
youall that are like why can't I just
send people to an offer so here's the
thing we have to understand the concept
of when we are marketing we have to send
traffic and generally we're going to
send it from social media but even if
it's not social media let's say that
it's it's a it's a JV partner you do
affiliate marketing you might do a
podcast uh it might be even from your
email you still need to send people to
some kind of a landing page okay so this
would be a landing page and what the
thing the reason why you send them to a
landing page is allows you to track you
can track where people are coming from
into the algorithms that are on the
social media platforms and then this
allows you
to
re Target
these people later and so the reason why
we want to retarget people later is
because if we have additional offers to
show them we can actually retarget for
up to 6 months at a
95% discount on the quote unquote paid
ads cost which is awesome so that allows
us to really do a lot of testing that
allows us to save a lot of money and
it's why it it can actually save you a
lot of headaches and trial and error and
struggle when you create a landing page
versus just sending people straight to
um a shopping cart or something for sale
as as far as that goes the other thing
is it nurtures trust and it builds trust
with you so one of the the only reason
why people buy from us is because they
trust that it's going to deliver value
and what we believe what they've
promised to us as far as that goes the
only reason why my clients trust me to
join my coaching program the client
growth accelerator or they join any of
the live events that we do and they
listen to what I teach or they watch
videos like this the only reason why you
would subscribe to this channel is
because you trust that as we put out
videos we're going to be providing you
consistent value consistently to get you
results and that's exactly what we do
every single day and that's why I show
up on these videos and I would encourage
you to keep watching them as we put them
out so a landing page is really really
cool because it's a it's a it's a it's a
vehicle it's not it's not like like a
car vehicle but it's a it's a it's a
place where you can centralize send
people whether you're on social media
whether it be a paid advertisement
whether it be organic traffic whether it
be a you could throw in even a blog post
you could throw in YouTube as far as
this goes okay so like for instance I
just I just want to show you this here
real quick I have two currently very
specific landing pages over at my
website number one I'm hosting an
incredible live event next week
Wednesday June 5th if you're watching
this after June 5th go to my website we
usually host a number of different
events we have different things that we
that you can check out different classes
that are on the homepage of my website
but this is the one that we're hosting
right now Wednesday June 5th is create
and launch your six-figure group
coaching Community offer without burnout
how you can do so on just 10 5 to 10
hours a week and our process of doing
that so this is a landing page this is
also what we would call A lead magnet it
simultaneously works as a lead magnet
because it's a free event that I'm
hosting but I'm sending people to it I'm
mentioning it even right now in this
video if you're watching this video I
think it would be a great fit for you
because it's exactly directly for the
people that watch these videos and so
name and email address this gets you on
my email list as far as this goes okay
so this is a lead magnet this is a
landing page that we've put together
that contains a few of the important
elements of a landing page we have uh a
headline right here we have a title for
it we have another headline right here
and this is a process that I found if
I'm running paid advertising that I want
to do is I really want this initial part
to be what helps people make a decision
of if they're on the right landing page
I'm looking for coaches course creators
mentors authors and trainers who want a
burnout free approach to make 5 to
25,000 per month while only working 10
to 15 hours a week loving every minute
of it the ultimate cure for Burnout and
overwhelm for coaches who want to make
real revenue and profits without selling
their soul and that's exactly exactly
what we walk you through right here now
here's a an actual headline right here
so this portion this this helps people
make a decision whoops at the top here
of is this for me so before they even go
further all of this at the top is about
helping the person make a decision of is
this for me is this actually what I what
I what I want
as far as that goes okay let's check out
another landing page this is for my
coaching program that we have a waiting
list on and and again if you're watching
this I'd also encourage you to jump on
the waiting list for this my client
growth accelerator we have a header here
we have the first action that I want
people to take because it's a it's a
very Split Second action join the
waiting list and then we have a headline
right here finally get on the fast track
to making six and seven figures in your
coaching or course business even if you
aren't techie don't have a following yet
or even have your offer figures fig out
let's grow your business together now
again I'm actually re recreating this
page but this is a landing page where it
tells people about what we offer what
we're selling what's included with our
coaching program all of those
features but our money back guarantee
which is slightly I have I it's jokingly
tongue and cheek slightly insane
ridiculous risk-free 30-day money back
guarantee why is that because almost
nobody is going to literally offer 30
days of their highlevel coaching program
that gives you everything for 30 days
with money back guarantee I do very few
people ever ask for their money back
because they find it to be so incredible
so all that to say these are landing
pages that are on my website so what you
want to do is that's really like what I
tell people is the first stage that we
want to get to when it comes to
marketing our our coaching or our course
business is we got to have pages that we
actually send people to and you notice I
only have really two right now that I'm
sending people to which is awesome sure
this is a Squarespace site right here if
you're wondering about the tech piece of
it I love Squarespace because it's very
simple here's another lead magnet right
here free chat GPT prompts uh love it
chat GPT 40 is now free these are some
of my best prompts that we've been using
for years that have generated us and our
clients eight figures so you can check
that out right there um and yeah I got
my blog and my podcast and all this um I
I also have like a free Facebook group
right here that you can go check
out but and that's another lead magnet
as well all that to say this is really
it's a very simple website there's not a
lot going on on here there's not a lot
of information connected on
here why is that
because it um it we focus in
on very specifically
where we want to send people I want
people to all roads lead to the email
list or signing up for our coaching
program as far as that goes and so even
if you listen to a podcast with me even
if you you watch a video with me I'm
always going to mention the different
offers that we have that's a word of
advice to you by the way and listen that
might feel uncomfortable for you you
might be annoyed right now and there's
literally people that logged off of this
video we see the statistics because I'm
mentioning the offers that I have I'm
trying to give you an example of how to
build it yourself but they got annoyed
by that fact because they're like he's
just trying to promote his stuff well
the
yeah it's what I'm teaching you how to
do exactly you get it so does that make
sense so what you got to do is you got
to get comfortable with the fact that
you are sending people to something that
they're going to sign up on that you're
going to capture their info that's going
to inform them that's going to also help
them make a buying decision and so what
we do is we want want to put some kind
of a landing page together there's a
structure to effective landing pages
that we've actually come up with that
nearly all of our landing pages follow
whether they're simple or not and and
and they always always have at the top
of them some kind of a headline in bold
letters and then some kind of a story
that breaks down and then a call to
action so this is a very simple landing
page you just have a simple headline
some text and then a call the action I
probably gotten like 4,000 leads off of
this chat gbt prompt
deal like hyper qualified people that
have downloaded this we have had people
tell us like like back in the day when
everybody was like charging $100 for the
chat gvt prompts I was like n nah I'm
going to give it away for free and I'm
going to literally load up an entire
document with you on the best sales copy
prompts that you can do that we
literally go through for your sales copy
for advertising we have some of the best
advertising prompts that are in here
finding your avatar finding your Niche
all these different
things and people are getting results
from it and it's incredible it's amazing
email marketing prts and so that's the
biggest thing that's one of the biggest
things that you want to do is your lead
magnet needs to be based on the
big
desire that you're mark Market has and
this is where I think a lot of people
get it wrong is they're trying to just
inform people they're trying to just
give people quote unquote what they want
or what they or I mean not what they
want what what they like as the coach if
you're a coach if you know what your
Market wants if you know what people
need necessarily a lot of the lead
magnets that I find that people do a lot
of their offers a lot of their landing
pages are are trying to communicate what
people need the the big picture thing
that people need right um but it's
disconnected from what people actually
want so we're not actually getting to
know what people actually want we're not
Gathering feedback as to what they want
and so this is where we got two
approaches that we can take with this we
can either use chat
GPT you can use AI to simulate it or you
can use uh
surveys and I like to use what I call
like a subtle survey approach where we
survey people
subtly when they sign up for things how
do I survey somebody subtly they can
sign up for an offer and I and and two
ways so like when somebody signs up for
one of my offers like
this right
here I have bonus trainings that I've
included with this you can see these
then they're literally complete bonus
trainings the ultimate Niche topic
picking
blueprint free bonus training two let's
let's create your Facebook ads
together free bonus three break out of
the cycle of overwhelm and worry for
good free bonus four picking the best
software platforms to build your
business on okay so these are bonus
trainings that are absolutely incredible
that we put together and so what I have
is for people to get access to those
once they sign up I'm just going to show
you kind of the process here of the lead
magnet number one we have a VIP upgrade
right here on this page
$17 that gives access to additional
bonuses additional things but let's go
check this out I'm just going to show
you this on the confirmation page here
and by the way you can take all these
pages that I have copy the text yourself
and use them for your own landing pages
I encourage people to do that literally
take all of my landing pages copy them
for yourself and then fill in kind of
your information as far as that goes
just make sure it doesn't say my info
there you go so what it is is it's a a
face group right here that people can
jump into and then in the Facebook group
is the bonus trainings so literally this
is a 51 minute Facebook ads training
where I broke down like that's a full
training on Facebook ads I break down
the ads manager and everything this is a
30 minute training on finding your Niche
this is a 23 minute training on breaking
out of the cycle of overwhelm this is a
really good training uh this is an
18-minute training on on how to pick the
best software platforms which ones are
out there my opinions on them as far as
that goes so like already I'm deliver
like I'm overd delivering value I'm
literally giving value of what most
people would charge for a course on and
we just launched this like yesterday we
already got uh 21 people that jumped in
the Facebook group I think we have close
to 70 that signed up on our lead magnet
since yesterday which is awesome that's
it's exactly those are the kind of
numbers we're looking for for our offers
that we know are hitting we know that
they're connecting because people are
taking action they want what we're
actually throwing down they want what
we're actually putting out there okay so
based on this we figured out the exact
needs that people want they want to know
all those things that are included in
the bonus offers and I also might create
a lead magnet that might be directly how
to launch your Facebook ads how to find
your Niche how to pick the best software
platforms how to break past overwhelm I
might even split these out into
additional other lead magnets later as
far as that goes whether they be
pre-recorded trainings or they might be
um um webinars live webinars or they
might be a hybrid where it's like a like
a multi-step class as far as that goes
so I've kind of taken advantage of that
is where I'm giving people anytime I'm
bringing people into my ecosystem I'm
always really giving them I'm overd
delivering on what they want and I'm
giving them what they
desire what most people charge money for
this is key what most most people would
actually charge for and you might be
saying well Jeremiah if I give away what
I would charge money for what would I
have left to sell them well that's where
we got to flip our perspective is realiz
is that your value when you're selling
to people goes far beyond the
information that you're offering people
we live in a world today with artificial
intelligence where information is very
easy to access you're on YouTube right
now you can literally find answers and
trainings that are free that go so deep
into different topics through you YouTu
but why do people invest with
me to coach with me to work with me in
my accelerator program because they get
access to me they're not just getting
the info they get to work with me I get
to join them in my in their business to
help build out their offers to build out
their landing pages to help make what
are the best decisions to put out there
what are the best things to to put in
the sales copy and the words that you
write and stuff like that okay so that's
what you want to do is you want to in
your free
offer and this is very very important we
found this through a lot of testing I'll
tell you a story one of my clients uh
his name was Rick we launched a program
and we couldn't seem to figure out what
the what the key connector between free
offers and paid offers were and then we
we literally we tested hundreds of
thousands of dollars in paid advertising
to figure this out and and then it was
so simple is what it was is whatever the
paid offer was whatever the free things
that we put out were and all of that
were so connected that it was literally
like
this free
offer paid offer and they were so
connected that they were a direct shot a
beline shot for the same thing so what
we ended up doing was is that our offer
that we charged for was essentially for
the same thing that our free offer was
let me explain this to you real quick
okay the free offer is going to be the
beginning steps of it it's going to have
an overview of what the process is but
there's always going to be
implementation nuance and additional
support and reasons why people want to
join whether it be a membership they
want a step-by-step process that goes
deeper than just what a single individ
idual training might offer to really get
specific about what this is it's nearly
impossible and and for those of y'all
maybe I'm I'm I'm I'm going like way
behind the curtain here for a lot of you
right now with what I'm about to say is
it's nearly impossible in a in a 1H hour
or a two-hour training to cover every
aspect of building a business but you
can give the foundations to help people
know if that's a path that they want to
take you you can show people that like
you're watching this video right now 19
minutes in I've covered a lot of ground
in this that most people reserve for
their highle masterminds and
yet um you know there's a deeper I bet
it's inspiring it's triggering different
questions that you might have make sure
to drop your questions in the comments
below that that this video might be
triggering and any of the videos that I
offer make sure to leave comments
because I want these to be an
interactive experience where we get we
get to talk back and forth about what
are you doing what are you creating how
do we put all of these pieces together
as far as that goes and so what what it
is is whether it be YouTube content
whether it be your free content you
always want it to inspire action to go
to the next level with you for the right
people now that's not everybody okay and
here's what you got to understand with
your free content 95% of the people who
engage with your free content are not
going to be buyers okay so I know that
95% of people that join my webinars that
engage with me that that take a look at
the stuff that I offer they're never
going to become a paid client of mine
and I'm not expecting them to because
I've been I've been at this long enough
to know that this is actually where it
boils down to a numbers game you
essentially will get about one in every
like 20 people that signs up for a free
offer that you put out there that
becomes a paid client and so you got to
really take that into account as well
with your pricing with how you're
pricing your offers and things like that
and that's exactly what we we're going
to be going over next week during that
live event so with this though that one
out of 20 people those are what we call
your
true um clients your true people your
true clients the ones who are really
committed to working with you they're
your upper echelon of people so if they
so you get all these people that sign up
for like free content but only about one
in 20 of those is going to like become a
client and and and we've grown email
list to like 200,000 people out of
200,000 how many became clients about 20
about uh no it was more than 10 thou
yeah it was about 10,000 became clients
of the main coaching program but I think
we had like
50,000 that bought like low ticket
offers that were like 7 to2 $7 as far as
that goes so that's the other thing too
you might have low ticket offers that
you offer you might have high ticket
offers where does the profit margin come
in it comes in by realizing that it is a
numbers game and then I really want to
focus in on who's that true group of
people what questions do they have how
can I serve them and then I create
content I create offers I create landing
pages that connect with what they want
as far as that goes okay so there's a
structure to putting together a lead
magnet landing page and that's this is
what I really like wanted to show you
here is anytime you put a landing page
together there's a few elements that you
want to make sure that it
has let's go click over here we want to
have something that identifies who it's
for a graphic you can make this in canva
we made this in canva canva.com is a
website where you can you can find a ton
of amazing templates and then put
Graphics together
they're all built into canva you can
literally type
in um webinar header for launching dog
walking
business right here
okay and then canva will go to
work to create you a graphic that you
could put at the top of of of a landing
page right here we can change the color
I like this one right here this one's
pretty cool you can customize this and
then you can turn this into the header
uh for for a dog walking business as far
as this goes so canva has the potential
to be able to do that for
you which is awesome okay now below this
we have our headline and then this is
what we call the storytelling section of
the page we have an image here and and
this one is actually this is an AI
generated image right here but it's
specifically geared towards my target
client we created this over at meta doai
I was able to type in and and and and
ask it questions
for who I want to I want to create
graphics for as far as this goes
different people that are in business we
tell it um you know different prompts as
far as what type of people we want and
so you can create stock photos and stuff
like that even over in meta AI these are
a lot of these are based off of photos
and stuff that are on Instagram that
they use to train the algorithm
for this so like on our landing page I
don't even buy stock photos anymore I'll
use photographs of me and then we this
is another photo right here and if I
told you that it's AI you can kind of
tell but like it's good enough that it
gets the story across that I'm trying to
get across and that's what I like about
the meta AI images is that they're good
enough for my landing pages that the
that the emotion comes across that I'm
trying to get there a healthy um vibrant
woman who's maybe in her her 40s to 50s
working on a computer uh a a couple that
is in their 40s to you know probably mid
40s that are happy in their office those
are the two images that I was looking
for as far as that goes so that's how I
was even describing it to the meta AI
then this is the storytelling section
right here and truthfully what I did was
I used chat GPT to help me come up with
some of the concepts for this
I went over to
Facebook and I looked at who were my
competitors and I was able to click on
their landing pages and their
offers to to read their sales copy I was
able to sign up for and even check out
on my swipe file my email list who is
marketing to a similar Market that I
have as well
right and then what are they putting on
their Pages what are their offers that
they're putting out there as far as
their lead magnets go what is the
language that they're using on their
headlines and then I was to able to
reverse engineer that back
into on my landing
page a very
simple offer stack right
here that breaks down what it is that
I'm teaching people what I'm going to
deliver to them it tells a story on
it a little bit about me right
here I've been in this industry it's a
Bio Section what I'm going to teach as
far as this
goes what they're going to get out of it
so this is you can make this as short or
as long as you want you might have
noticed some of those landing pages I
clicked on they had really short lead
magnet Pages generally those are going
to be vssl landing pages on the other
side of those they might have a short
like 30 minute video similar to this
YouTube video that then leads people to
sign up for something that's like a
longer offer like this and this is more
something that you might Reserve to send
to to your email list as far as that
goes so there's a number of different
like landing pages and Lead magnet
styles that we put together but the
thing that they all have in common is
they all speak to the desire that the
prospect actually wants they speak to
the exact desire that the person who's
out there is looking for that they're
searching for that they're trying to
find the answers to
and then people sign up and join the
email list to get that answer now the
problem is a lot of the lead magnets
that are out there they don't even
deliver on a lot of the promises that
you make so if you're somebody who
actually can deliver on what you promise
in your lead magnet and you're actually
somebody with Integrity who's not
wasting people's time you're actually
showing up to the table with something
of value to people and it's what people
actually want and it's not just a giant
sales pitch right anybody who watches my
webinars know we don't just have a it's
not just a big pitchfest it's not just a
bunch of testimonials as far as that
goes now we have people that might
prejudge what I do as saying that but
those that are willing to take a risk
with me to listen to what I have to
share they're the more qualified true
people that I'm actually looking for so
one of the biggest things you got to
realize when it comes to your lead
magnet is this you're not going to get
everybody anybody who has a pulse what
you really want is you want to qualify
the people that are going to be a good
fit for what you have to offer the
algorithms actually read the text that's
on your landing page to decide is this
for this person or that person they read
the text that's in your ads they read
the text that you put on your social
media post to decide who to show your
offer to you might say I don't have any
text in my social media post so the
algorithms actually transcribe all the
words that you say and they're analyzing
with AI all the stuff that you say in
videos right now YouTube has a
transcript of this video right here to
decide who to show it to as far as that
goes people just like you that are
looking for this type of content and so
then from there people are able to make
a decision that they want to sign up and
register or
engage based on the fact that it fits
exactly what they're looking for there's
a there's a direct fit
to the the thing that they desire and
then if you can build trust with people
in that you can sell them on what your
thing is that you're offering so one of
the biggest mistakes people make when
they're actually creating an offer is
they're like I'm just going to get a
bunch of people on my email list and
then they're going to eventually go to
my website and they're going to buy from
me that can be that's one of the wrong
perspectives on this that's one of the
biggest mistakes that I see a lot of
people make when it comes to their email
list when it comes to the tech aspects
of putting together their landing pages
is they're thinking about it from this
very passive approach you have to think
about it from a direct response
marketing approach okay there's a great
book that I love on this it's right here
behind me called The Ultimate Sales
letter by Dan Kennedy it's about the
direct response marketing approach to
writing sales copy and so what you want
to do is we use whoops the photo fell we
use artificial intelligence to help us
brainstorm ideas using those prompts
that I just showed you to then put and
and what I'll do generally is I will
most of the ideas that the AI produces
now for landing pages I don't like but
I'll rewrite it in my own words and I'll
also take a look at what are other
people putting out there that are online
that are on social media other offers
that they're putting out there and I'm
able to decide okay like here's an offer
right here this one's a little bit more
of a longer form one like I
have what are the what are some of the
headlines that they're using and I'm
going to and I'm going to use that as
ideas for what to create for my offer
for my Marketplace I look at the
structure of other landing pages that
are out there so we want to mirror the
structure we got the headline of who
it's for that's very important we have
the headline of what's going to be
taught we have an image with a title for
it and then we we dive deeper into after
we Peak the interest of people diving
deeper into who it's for who it's not
for and delivering on the outcome so
every landing page everything that's
going to grow in email list answers all
of those questions for people on one
page and then people sign up for it to
get some kind of value delivered to them
some kind of value that they're going to
be able to take away from it to be able
to go get results in their business okay
so as far as this goes that's exactly
what we want to come up with and that's
exactly what I work with people on in my
accelerator program that's that it's a
little bit more nuanced than what I can
teach you right here in in this training
I'm I might make another training
specifically on just the sales copy side
of it in fact actually in fact we do
have actually did one let me go find it
it's over in my YouTube channel right
here if you go check out my YouTube
videos I'm going to go find the one I'm
going to go find the date of where it's
at I'm going to literally pull it up
right here of probably what what what
the next video to watch after this is
that's going to answer this for you is
what do you put in your sales copy $100
million copyrighting Secrets this was
from 2 weeks ago you can see the cover
right here $100 million copyright
Secrets or I'm smiling right there or I
have the book right there and I break
down in about 47
minutes how to come up
with the sales copy what is the process
of writing the sales copy as far as that
goes so you can check that video out as
well right here I'm going to copy the
link to it as well and put it in the
description
below okay so all of that to say when
you're building your landing page out
when you're building out that we can use
a very simple landing page builder like
a Squarespace site you you create a
canva graphic we start to brainstorm our
sales copy we start to learn how do we
communicate exactly what's going to
connect with people and then we get them
to sign up for something that we're
going to deliver generally in the form
of a video piece of content or it could
also be an ebook or a checklist or
something that people will sign up for
and then what that's going to do is now
that they're on your email list you can
send emails to them to engage with them
to get them to sign up for additional
offers so they might sign up for an
ebook over here okay but then I might
send them to a webinar offer via an
email and retarget them with ads for a
webinar offer but then all roads lead to
seeing are they one of my true clients
that really wants to engage with me to
purchase what I'm offering so we're
being very intentional once people join
the email list we're being very
intentional to get them to take action
to move forward with us to move along
I'm leading them I'm I'm corralling them
towards every single person who engages
with me I'm trying to Corral you towards
creating your offer that's the number
one step that I start every people
everybody at we got trainings that we
launch on creating your
offer we have a number of video
trainings on my YouTube channel in my
coaching program I work with you to put
your offer together and so if that's
something that you would like to work
with me on again join if you're able to
join the event that we're doing on June
5th next week so over at my website
jeremi Kowski decom you can find the
link to that in the bio and then get on
the waiting list for my coaching program
the client growth accelerator program so
that when we open the doors to that when
we have enrollment that's open to that
you get to work with me personally not
somebody else not a team member but you
actually get to personally work with me
to put your offers together to dial in
your ads to build out your landing pages
to build out your lead magnets you to
work with me as part of your team to get
all of this put together and I'd love to
do that with you to help you reach those
results those goals that you're looking
for six figures the clients who work
with us they start to get those kind of
results that's what I want to help you
with as well and I want to walk you
through that process and come alongside
you to create those kind of results in
your business so join the waiting list
and I'd love to work with you and St
subscribed to this Channel and let's
keep working together to help you grow
your business and get more results we'll
talk soon have a good one